Rasoul Shahriary	Web Developer
Address	Dalføret 15,st mf
City, Country	Copenhagen, Denmark
Mobile	+45 93990483
Email	Rasoul.Shahriary@gmail.com
Date and Place of Birth	1984 – Iran
Linkedin	https://dk.linkedin.com/in/rasoulsh



Profile

IT professional with more than 6 years' experience in developing and supporting web applications. Responsible for Developing the front end functionality of Customer's websites with CSS, JavaScript and Photoshop for 2 years. Have been working 4 years as part of a supporting team, carrying out ad-hoc tasks as requested by customers, Had a specific brief to ensure the websites build for customer's precisely matched their requirements and their local web server work properly all the time.

Work Experience

Apr 2012-Aug 2014	Front End Developer	Isiran Software Company
Apr 2012-Aug 2014	Front End Developer	Isiran Software Compa

Isiran Software Company is one of the biggest software companies in Iran. The major activities are analyzing and designing and implementing desktop and web application; managing and monitoring integrating software in country level and educating IT and language programming.

My responsibilities:

- Involved in creating a web based official automation.
- Maintained existing websites and made required changes in the HTML, CSS and JavaScript codes
- Developed and maintained the front end functionality of websites.
- Participated in discussions with clients to clarify what they want.
- Creating logos, banners and buttons for websites using Adobe Photoshop.
- Simultaneously managed several databases and reporting tools
- Provided technical support to end users.
- Developed a minor car sale web site with PHP at university as a project.
- Made several minor web pages using bootstrap framework

Designed and developed websites using HTML, CSS, , jQuery and Photoshop

Projects:

www.isiportal.ir

www.isishop.ir

www.isiran-net.ir

https://github.com/rasoul-shahriari/

Jan 2008-Apr 2012

IT Web consultant

Isiran Software Company

Responsibilities

- Supported a web based official Automation.
- Used CSS and JS to make Change website to meet customer's need.
- Installed, tuned and configured VMware workstation.
- Installed and configured IIS as a webserver.
- Supported, made backup and maintained Database servers (Microsoft SQL).
- Worked at Service desk and helpdesk support.
- Worked at 1st and 2nd level support.
- Performed maintenance and updates to existing client Web sites
- Helped end users to solve operating problems
- Documented software and technical specifications like FAQ list
- Provided guidance and advice to less experienced staff

Education

2005- Associate's Degree in Computer Software Engineering – Shahid Shamsipour Technical College (Iran)

2012 - BSc in Computer Software Engineering - Islamic Azad University (Iran)

Skills

- CSS
- Java script
- jQuery
- HTML
- Photoshop
- PHP
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- C++

Web server:

- Microsoft IIS Server
- XAMPP Server

Methodologies:

• Object Oriented Programming

Database servers

- Microsoft SQL Server
- My SQL Server

Operating system

- Windows 7
- Windows 8
- Windows Server 2003,2008 and 2012
- Linux Ubuntu and Mint

Languages

Persian Native

English Professional working proficiency

Danish Elementary